Guide to the Johnnie Parrish papers, 1979-1994.
Parrish, Johnnie papers, 1979-1994
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Johnnie Parrish papers, 1979-1994.
6570
Johnnie Parrish
3 cubic ft.
Notes, clippings, publications, videotapes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Files for Focus on Art include notes, clippings, publications, and other background materials for the television shows, compiled by Johnnie Parrish. Also, original videotapes of the shows that included interviews with local artists as well as workshops and gallery openings. Also, alphabetical subject files on art and artists. Copy of Seventeen magazine, July 1953, with article mentioning Priscilla Kiefer (Johnnie Parrish)
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Focus on Art was a weekly cable program, hosted by Priscilla A. (Johnnie) Parrish in Ithaca from 1979 to 1987.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Files for Focus on Art include notes, clippings, publications, and other background materials for the television shows, compiled by Johnnie Parrish. Also, original videotapes of the shows that included interviews with local artists as well as workshops and gallery openings. Also, alphabetical subject files on art and artists.
Copy of Seventeen magazine, July 1953, with article mentioning Priscilla Kiefer (Johnnie Parrish)
SUBJECTS
Names:
Parrish, Johnnie.
Subjects:
Art--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Artists--New York (State)--Ithaca.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
See also Jason Seley Papers, #15-1-3069
CONTAINER LIST
- T.V. May 1979-May 1980, I (Box 1, Folder 1)
- T.V. May 1979-May 1980, II (Box 1, Folder 2)
- T.V. May 1979-May 1980, III (Box 1, Folder 3)
- T.V. May 1979-May 1980, IV (Box 1, Folder 4)
- May 1979-May 1980, V (Box 1, Folder 5)
- T.V. May 1979-May 1980, VI (Box 1, Folder 6)
- T.V. Sept. 1980-Jan 1981, I (Box 1, Folder 7)
- T.V. Sept. 1980-Jan 1981, II (Box 1, Folder 8)
- T.V. Sept. 1980-Jan 1981, III (Box 1, Folder 9)
- T.V. Sept. 1980-Jan 1981, IV (Box 1, Folder 10)
- T.V. Sept. 1980-Jan 1981, V (Box 1, Folder 11)
- T.V. Feb 1981-May 1981, I (Box 1, Folder 12)
- T.V. Feb 1981-May 1981, II (Box 1, Folder 13)
- T.V. Feb 1981-May 1981, III (Box 1, Folder 14)
- T.V. Feb 1981-May 1981, IV (Box 1, Folder 15)
- T.V. Feb 1981-May 1981, V (Box 1, Folder 16)
- T.V. Feb 1981-May 1981, VI (Box 1, Folder 17)
- T.V. Feb 1981-May 1981, VII (Box 1, Folder 18)
- What's Happening? 1981 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Focus on Art 1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- T.V. Sept. 1981-Dec 1981, I (Box 1, Folder 21)
- T.V. Sept. 1981-Dec 1981, II (Box 1, Folder 22)
- T.V. Sept. 1981-Dec 1981, III (Box 1, Folder 23)
- T.V. Sept. 1981-Dec 1981, IV (Box 1, Folder 24)
- T.V. Sept. 1981-Dec 1981, V (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Video Dialogue 1981 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- What's Happening? 1982 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Focus on Art 1982 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- T.V. Jan 1982-May 1982, I (Box 1, Folder 29)
- T.V. Jan 1982-May 1982, II (Box 1, Folder 30)
- T.V. Jan 1982-May 1982, III (Box 1, Folder 31)
- T.V. Jan 1982-May 1982, IV (Box 1, Folder 32)
- T.V. Jan 1982-May 1982, V (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Focus on Art Sept. 1982-May 1983 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- What's Happening? 1982-1983, I (Box 1, Folder 35)
- What's Happening? 1982-1983, II (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Focus on Art 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- T.V. Sept. 1982-May1983, I (Box 1, Folder 38)
- T.V. Sept. 1982-May1983, II (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Focus on Art Sept. 1983-May 1984 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- What's Happening? 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- T.V. Sept. 1983-May 1984, I (Box 1, Folder 42)
- T.V. Sept. 1983-May 1984, II (Box 1, Folder 43)
- T.V. Sept. 1983-May 1984, III (Box 1, Folder 44)
- T.V. Sept. 1983-May 1984, IV (Box 1, Folder 45)
- T.V. Sept. 1983-May 1984, V (Box 1, Folder 46)
- T.V. Sept. 1983-May 1984, VI (Box 1, Folder 47)
- T.V. Sept. 1983-May 1984, VII (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Focus on Art Sept. 1984-May 1985 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- What's Happening? 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- T.V. Sept. 1984-May 1985, I (Box 1, Folder 51)
- T.V. Sept. 1984-May 1985, II (Box 1, Folder 52)
- T.V. Sept. 1984-May 1985, III (Box 1, Folder 53)
- T.V. Sept. 1984-May 1985, IV (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Publicity Feb. 1987-May 1987 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- What's Happening? 1987 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- T.V. Feb. 1987-May 1987, I (Box 1, Folder 57)
- T.V. Feb. 1987-May 1987, II (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Area Video Archives 1979-1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Focus on Art 1979- (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Focus on Art-The Artist's Psyche, The Creative Process-I (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Focus on Art-The Artist's Psyche, The Creative Process-II (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Area Video Archives, I (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Area Video Archives, II (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Area Video Archives, III (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Area Video Archives, IV (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Area Video Archives, V (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Area Video Archives, VI (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Area Video Archives, VII (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Recognition for Focus on Art (Box 2, Folder 12)
- San Francisco Museum of Modern Art 50th Anniversary (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Will Barnet (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Drawings (Box 2, Folder 15)
- See all 'Focus Shows,' Kenneth Evett (Box 2, Folder 16)
- See all 'Focus Shows,' John Hartell (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Hnizdovsky (Box 2, Folder 18)
- H. Peter Kahn (Box 2, Folder 19)
- P (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Porters (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Prints (Box 2, Folder 22)
- R (Box 2, Folder 23)
- S (Box 2, Folder 24)
- See " Focus" #100, Jason Seley (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Sculpture (Box 2, Folder 26)
- T (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Tate (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Techniques (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Turner (Box 2, Folder 30)
- U (Box 2, Folder 31)
- V (Box 2, Folder 32)
- W (Box 2, Folder 33)
- X,Y,Z (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Reproduction of a photo depicting 3 female students in the tracery of the War Memorial on West Campus (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Larger reproduction of a photo depicting 3 female students in the tracery of the War Memorial on West Campus, O/S Folder
- miscellaneous articles and letters (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Seventeen magazine, July 1953 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- CAVCL (umatic full size format), V-5931 (Box 3)
- CAVCL (VHS), V-5932 (Box 3)
- Poems (umatic small size format), V-5933 (Box 3)
- Focus on Art – H. Peter Kahn, Ancient Glass, John Hartell, Printmaking, Jason Seley: Celebration of Sculpture (VHS), V-5934 (Box 3)
- Focus on Art – Jason Seley: Celebration of Sculpture - repeat (VHS), V-5935 (Box 3)
- Focus on Art – H. Peter Kahn (VHS), V-5936 (Box 3)
  mix up: actually WCNY broadcast of The Three Tenors
- Ameritech, "William Wordsworth and the Age of English Romanticism" (VHS), V-5937 (Box 3)
- "A Tribute to H. Peter Kahn", 1997 (VHS), V-5938 (Box 3)
- 2 cassettes, Ed Bryant on Jason Seley, TR-9249-9250 (Box 3)